Data can now live together with this
Good afternoon.
Today we have a song from our 32nd single
With three of us standing up the slide of tears
We're here to go down the slide
We are here to go down the slide.
While we're sliding down the slide
I heard that that little tear slide is flowing.
That's right.
I'm hoping to do a lot of sliding today.
I see.
Please come along.
I'm looking forward to it.
First, we came to Mito Forest Park.
It's a long way!
Let's ski a lot!
Let's go skiing!
It's raining!
We came down in the rain, didn't we?
Yeah, we arrived, looked out, and the windows started to get wet.
Ayame, have you ever heard of a woman of sunshine?
I'm quite the sunny girl.
So have I, by the way.
Me too.
We're all here.
I'm going.
Thank you very much.
You're leaving, aren't you?
Come here.
Walk.
Really?
I think I'll just stay here.
I feel like I'm 12 years old.I feel like I'm 12 years old.
Precentage?
I feel like I'm 12.
No, really.
But I'm 16 today.
Oh, yes, that's right.
Congratulations!
Thank you.
Today's your birthday?
Your 16th birthday?
Yes, it is.
Sixteen. Sixteen.
He said when he was 16.
What was it?
One more time?
Do you remember?
Not really.
I don't remember much either.
You weren't like this, Babu.
I know.
You're a bub.
Babu?
Why is she so cute?
How tall are you?
Five-four.
Five-four?
I guess that's the point.
Yes, that's not all.
It's not just that.
She's cute.
What's cute about Aya?
She holds her hands in a "goo" position longer than other people.
I know.
I know what you mean.
She has a habit of making her hands gooey.It's a habit of yours, isn't it?
It's a habit.
Like when you're walking.
It's kind of tacky, so I'm going to stop doing it.
It's not tacky? It's kind of cute.
Your fingers are short.
Are they?
Yes, they are.
Your hands are like babies.
They're so cute.
Oh, wow.
They're so tiny.
It's so tiny, but...
It's so cute!
That's amazing.
It's so small... so tiny.
I'm tiny, too.
Oh, you're right.
But why are you so cute?
Oh, no.
Oh, no!
Oh, the watermelon...
It's close. It's close.
Two seconds.
Like a baby on top of a baby.
There's one that looks like a baby ride.
Like a bumpy version of Thomas.
There is one.
Yes, there is.
Oh, I see what you mean.
What do we do now?
You're gonna get soaked.
Yes, that's fine.
It's raining.
Can we stop this for a minute?I don't think I should do this.
I'm not going to do it.
There's one more thing.
Yes, I do.
This one?
A slide.
Rollers.
Pretty steep, huh?
Looks a little scary.
Yeah.
Sounds fun.
Shall we go?
I said I wanted to do it.
I'll go first.
You want to go?
Okay.
Have fun.
You want to slide?
Do you want me to lift you up?
Oh, you're scaring me.
My butt.
Is it slippery?
Let me just get in there.
Have a good day.
Wow!
I'm coming in.
I'm coming.
What's that?
Uh, uh, uh...
Uh-oh.
Ha-ha-ha.
You're skiing slowly.
Maybe if we go slow, we can buy some time.
I'm slipping I'm slipping I'm slipping
Because the last thing you want to do is slide.Because the last thing I want is to slide.
Because I like to flow
I slipped at the end
Cave Thrust 2 Lord
Posil is Ee provoker
Shutter
Estimer this
Can't you just get in there? Don't put your butt on it.
It comes from me.
I've got the back of the shoe.
Oh, you can go.
You sure?
No.
Hey, how long does it take to go down a slide?
What's he doing?
Okay, okay.
When Ayumu was second on the slide...
When we got off, she was standing next to me.
She was such a big sis.
What? Really?
I'm so happy.
She's my sister.
It's a dinosaur.
Oh, my God.
Dinosaurs.
Dinosaurs!
They really existed once, didn't they?
They sure did.
Wow.
Wow!
It's huge.
It's not in the picture.
It really is.
It's cute.
It's cute.Cute.
Wow!
It's huge!
It's huge.
That's huge!
It's huge!
It's huge, isn't it?
Bigger than this front desk.
Yes, it is, isn't it?
Here it is.
Wow.
It's so short.
It's so big.
It's such a big one.
Here it comes.
All right, let's go down the slide.
It's okay.
Let's see if I can do it.
Ready?
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Oh!
That looks pretty painful.
Oh, my God.
It's been, like, four years.
But you're gonna get your ass dirty.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
I'm off to work.
Have a good day.
How'd it go?
I don't know... my stomach...
It's so dark.
I never thought I'd spend so much time
I thought Renka...I'm afraid that a lot of people are
scared.
Please hang in there.
I'm scared.
yikes!
ohoh?
Aaah!
Hey, this is pretty scary.
It sure feels more slippery than before.
I feel like I'm slipping.
I'm off then.
I'm scared.
Have fun... the rain is getting lighter.
I'm sure it is.
I'm nervous.
Aya.
I hear you.
I can hear you.
That's great!
You're safe.
Oh, thank God!
We're here.
Good night.
Let's go!
Yay!
Mmm-hmm.
Welcome home.
Hi!
Done.
That was fun.
This is fun.
You didn't slide at all earlier.
I did it so hard with my hands.
I finally did it.I finally skied!
Yay!
Shall we go next?
Okay.
Yes, sir.
Now to Oku-Hitachi Kirara no Sato.
Here we are!
Wow!
It looks like there's a slide here, too!
The rain has stopped.
Yes, it did!
We won.
Let's go.
What's that? Is it already here? Oh, here it is.
Some kind of slide. The longest slide in Japan.
The longest slide in Japan. 1188 meters long.
1,188 meters? A kilometer.
Wow, wacky climber!
It's a little scary. It's a little nerve-wracking.
The mountains are great. It's easy to see.
Here, let's get ready. You want some paint? Is this your first time?
You don't want to paint, okay? It's okay. Are you sure you're okay?
It's not heat? No fever? Are you sure?
Okay, I'll go.
I'm in the middle of something.
Cute. I'll do my best.
Cute baby.
This way, please.
Go to the front of the line, please.
Cute. There's the baby.
Okay, let's go.
Let's give her lots of levers to roll.
Off you go.
Are you okay? Bye-bye.Is everything okay? Bye-bye.
That's pretty fast.
That's good. Maybe a little scary.
Fast, fast, fast.
Beautiful. Watch it, it's dangerous.
Pretty fast. Fast, fast, fast.
Brake on sharp turns.
Like this.
I overdid it a little bit.
I didn't think...
That was fast! That was fast!
Oh, no! Too fast!
Let's go slowly.
Oh, there he is!
Too slow!
Looks slow!
I think we should go fast here.
Oh, maybe just a little bit.
This is the part where you don't fall off.
sharp turn brakes!
Wow, butterflies.
Already a white butterfly
Whoa, sharp curve sharp curve
Wow, wow, wow!
I'm really slanting my body
It's beautiful
Oh, I'm getting used to it.
Maybe a little more.
This could be fun.
Wow, you're going a little fast.
I was going a little too fast.
I can't go!
It's going really slow, like this.
Because I'm going to fall down a little bit.
Go faster here.
Take your speed.Take your speed.
Can you see it?
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Roll.
Whee-hee-hee-hee!
Whew!
Wow!
I'm so happy today, I'm really happy too.
I was in tears on the pusher.
I was so happy when they decided on the unit song.
For the first time, I felt happy to be the biggest superstar.
Oh, oh...
Oh, no.
I'll take that.
He's so cute!
She's so cute.
Aww, cute.
Cute.
Welcome home
I'm back.
Was it fun?
It was fun.
You're so cute.
Next time.
Let's wrap it up.
Close?
Closing.
Wow.
Let's wrap it up.
Well then...
Mr. Maeyama, until June.
Why?
Because it's June.
I'm off.
Bye bye.Bye-bye.
Good luck and have fun.
I'll have fun.
I'll give you one practice run.
Oh, I'm fine.
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
That's great.
Have a good day.
You're early.
Wow!
That was fast.
Come on.
Oh!
Ooh!
Game! Games!
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha.
Cool.
Good, that cycle is good!
Wow, nature at its best!
That's what I'm talking about.
It's fun.
Wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow.
That was fast!
We're at the finish line.
I'll be back.
Thank you very much.
Pretty flower.
Pretty.
I like it.I like it.
There's something in there.
Dirt.
What?
It's just a tail.
Just the tail and the butt.
I see it. I see it.
Oh! What? What?
You're lying.
It's so natural. It's so natural.
That was amazing.
It was a lot of fun.
You went so fast.
I went really fast.
I didn't think so.
Wasn't it scary?
Not at all.
I saw something that looked like an aardvark.
What?
I don't know what an aardvark is.
But when I was coming up, I saw something I'd never seen before.
Was it alive?
It was moving.
It was scary.
It felt so natural.
You felt it?
It's good that you felt it.
Okay, put him down.
I'm off.
That's great.
Okay, bye. First sled.
Good night.
Okay, go ahead.
I'm off.
Wow, you're stiff.Wow, stiff body
mustn
pou dou dou
Yoo-hoo!
Wow, birds, birds, birds
That kind of performance
Wow.
The angle of the body is amazing.
Oh, that's fun.
Oh, man.
Elvette...
It was so loose.
I'm afraid of curves.
Curves are fun.
I don't know.
You have to be good at stopping.
The course
to stop on its own.
easy to understand
Hey, hey, hey.
Elvette.
Oh, no.
Mr. Major...
Ogawa's suggestion.
I'm thinking of shooting a YouTube project.
I got something like
something like this.
I love the members of Tear Slide, so
I'd like to go on various slides with the three of us
I want to slide on various slides
but it's Ogawa's proposal
This is Ogawa's proposal.
Please enjoy it and go with him.
I got a call like that.
It was just too cute.He's just too cute.
It was so cute that I was super tired.
But I was so healed.
Look at this group!
Oh! Isn't this the goal?
Welcome back.
Thank you very much.
Here you go.
Ah!
Meikka...
Welcome back.
So cute!
Like sisters.
They really are.
What is it?
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
She's saying something.
I don't know.
Can we go home?
I wonder if we can go home.
A-ha-ha!
Yay!
We went down the longest slide in Japan!
It was fun.
How was your day?
Well, it was fun just because it was Mayan's idea.
I'm glad.
It's not often that the three of us do something together.
That's right.
Ayame.
Was it me?
How was it?
Well, I had fun, too.
It was kind of therapeutic.
Yes, it was healing.
Aya and Zue healed me too.Aya and Zue healed me
It was the time to just admire Ayamen.
I was so happy!
I was so happy to slide down the slides with Ayame and Nenkai!
I'm so happy!
I was so happy!
Since we slid down the slides so much
I'm sure you all heard a lot of tears on the slides.
I'd be happy if you could continue to listen to it!
All right!
Please do!
Then please subscribe to our channel!
Please subscribe to our channel.
I'd like to do something with the three of us again.
I'm sure we will.
Bye bye!